What do brokers say on this?
After the results, you showed a conference call
and the management talked about many new
segments. Till
UBS's question is, their target here is
Rs 1350. Because the price alone shows you a
return potential of about 40-50%.
This will be clearly visible. Even as far as the
company is concerned, there is an attempt to diversify both B2B and B2C i.e.
business and consumer by
joining hands with Reliance. And
somewhere the results of this quarter
were a little, but going forward, plants of a very big company are
seen happening. Citi
's target is Rs 825. Somewhere the group will be seen
strengthening and melioration.
And here also, if you look at the
new initiatives, there is strange demand,
you will see progress here too. There is a slow pace,
but the management's other problems regarding the
business
seem to be getting stronger. That is why many of these
features are positive because Just Dial is also
a group company of Reliance Industries.
Majority of the soil is Reliance Industries
and that should
maintain the dominance and proficiency of network18 tv18 watching this voice
it is a question of numbers and this is
Mughal soldiers orbit call symptoms nineteen
hundred rupees results are a little bit moral and
writing profit if you talk about it was as per
estimates Meena as far as
motor insurance is concerned here we have
seen a little bit of a decline
this normalization is being done by the
British and commentary as far as if the
management had
talked well about our group on the conference call with Vansh
so maybe these results are but the outlook is fine
and that is why waste oil towards use sand
remains luck as I told him earlier 19
Shubhendu Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal